Host: Good evening. Welcome to Quiz Night.
Our first contestant is Eddie from Washington, D.C.
Hi, Eddie. Are you nervous?
Eddie: No, not really.
I think I’m, uh, ready.
Host: Well, let’s hope so.
The rules are the same as always.
I’m going to read you some sentences, and you have ten seconds to say
if the sentence is true or false.
If you get the first answer right, you win one hundred dollars.
Then for each correct answer, you double your money,
so if you get the second answer right, you win two hundred dollars,
and for the third correct answer, you win four hundred dollars.
For eight correct answers, you win twelve thousand eight hundred dollars.
But if you get an answer wrong, you lose all the money.
Remember, you can also call a friend, so if you’re not sure about one of the answers,
you can call your friend to help you.
Is that OK, Eddie?
Eddie: Yeah, OK.